<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Words on andypbrowne</title>
    <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Words on andypbrowne</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://andypbrowne.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Always Be Recommending Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Did you just say podcast? You’ve got my attention How do you find new podcasts? For me, discovery never happens by just browsing a podcast app. I am always looking for personal recommendations or hot tips on my twitter feed. In the spirit of relevant recommendations, I am offering my go-to podcasts and favorite episodes broken down into mostly nonsensical categories of Road Trip, Morning Commuting, Sleep Aids, and Design Learning (Because I am a UX Designer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facilitating LEGO® SERIOUSPLAY®</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/workshopfacilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/workshopfacilitation/</guid>
      <description>LEGOs® can put corporate colleagues on the therapy couch   LEGO® SERIOUSPLAY® uses special sets of neutral bricks because themed bricks may carry too much meaning
  In the second half of 2018, my colleagues and I played with LEGO® bricks in a corporate setting for a total of 16 hours. Many were open to the idea because they thought it would be fun and make for good team building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insta Strategy</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/instastrategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/instastrategy/</guid>
      <description>Six types of instagram posts for artists and creative professionals to promote their work  Instagram a a social media platform has emerged a the most authentic way to represent yourself online. It&#39;s simplicity and format provide a built-in bullshit filter. As a bonus, the interface makes the process of discovery, curation and promotion intuitive and user-friendly.  If we could only choose one social media platform it should be Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moments</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/moments/</guid>
      <description>Short text and images inspired by the now defunct hi.co. These quick sketches are quick meditations in the spirit of fugitive ground &amp;lt;p class=&amp;quot;type underline&amp;quot;&amp;gt;August 12, 2016 &amp;amp;dash; Moment&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt; A man laboriously moves his piano down three levels onto the subway platform. Classic vocals and strided chords &amp;amp;mdash; he played so well I swore he was blind. Oblivious to the heat on that August stage, he was most in touch with his audience &amp;amp;mdash; whom he elevated with his music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data 2 Go</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/data2go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/data2go/</guid>
      <description>A summary of a Hyperact lunch talk about the creation of a web-based app called data2go.nyc   Data2go lunch talk notes and poster
  On Friday, 20 May 2016, Hyperact hyperakt.com/lunch-talks/ hosted a lunch talk with speaker Kristen Lewis. Kristen is the Co-director of Measure of America — an organization that provides easy-to-use yet methodologically sound tools for understanding the distribution of well-being and opportunity in America and stimulating fact-based dialogue about issues we all care about: health, education, and living standards measureofamerica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory of the SSMAC of New York City</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/ssmac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/ssmac/</guid>
      <description>The club’s mission states: Serving the men and women of our Armed Forces since 1919 — the club served me in my transition out of the military  Lounge at the SSMAC
   I have a strong connection between my transition out of the military and the The Soldiers&amp;rsquo;, Sailors&amp;rsquo;, Marines&amp;rsquo;, Coast Guard and Airmen&amp;rsquo;s Club (SSMAC) in New York City. Located on Lexington Avenue between 36th and 37th Streets, the SMAC wonderfully represents the strong connection NYC has to the uniformed services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Observing The Centennial</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/observing-the-cenntenial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/observing-the-cenntenial/</guid>
      <description>One hundred years later media, maps, websites and organizations to guide your commemoration of the war to end all wars WWI Soldiers in a dead Forest
From 2014 to 2018 we commemorate the centennial of &amp;#8220;The Great War,&amp;#8221; so-called because those who experienced it could imagine no conflict more terrible, and could not believe that the same disastrous mistakes could ever be repeated. Removed by as much as three generations from life today, the events of 1914&amp;#8211;18 hold lessons and truths about our humanity that could be lost&amp;#8202;&amp;#8212;&amp;#8202;or worse&amp;#8202;&amp;#8212;&amp;#8202;be rendered unbelievable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Day is not Memorial Day</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/veteransdayisnotmemorialday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/veteransdayisnotmemorialday/</guid>
      <description>Meaningful dialog on this often misunderstood holiday is needed — we need to change the narrative and start to really understand what these holidays are about I was moved the other day by a radio story about a gold-star family (NPR) who lost their son, however, the story would have been more appropriate on Memorial Day. Overall, we need to change the narrative and start to really understand what these holidays (in this case Veterans Day) are about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surrealist Drawing Techniques</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/surrealistdrawingtechniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/surrealistdrawingtechniques/</guid>
      <description>A collection of drawing methods to exercise the mind and the role of the subconcious in art and design   Example frottage work from the Golden Gate Bridge
  Frottage Frottage from the French frotter, “to rub,” is a surrealist technique developed by Max Ernst. In Frottage the artist takes a pencil or other drawing tool and makes a rubbing over a textured surface. The resulting drawing can be used as-is, or used as a base for further refinement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Fontana, New Media Artist</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/fontana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/fontana/</guid>
      <description>An artist’s installations making use of sound as a sculptural medium to transform the audience’s perceptions of visual and architectural settings Bill Fontana is a bit dry in interviews but he is big on sound. Bill attended the New School in New York City and studied music and philosophy. He is trained and practiced as a composer but he is known internationally for creating sound art. These installations use sound as a sculptural medium to transform the audience’s perceptions of visual and architectural settings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>