<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on andypbrowne</title>
    <link>https://andypbrowne.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on andypbrowne</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:42:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://andypbrowne.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Always Be Recommending Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Did you just say podcast? You’ve got my attention How do you find new podcasts? For me, discovery never happens by just browsing a podcast app. I am always looking for personal recommendations or hot tips on my twitter feed. In the spirit of relevant recommendations, I am offering my go-to podcasts and favorite episodes broken down into mostly nonsensical categories of Road Trip, Morning Commuting, Sleep Aids, and Design Learning (Because I am a UX Designer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facilitating LEGO® SERIOUSPLAY®</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/workshopfacilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/workshopfacilitation/</guid>
      <description>LEGOs® can put corporate colleagues on the therapy couch   LEGO® SERIOUSPLAY® uses special sets of neutral bricks because themed bricks may carry too much meaning
  In the second half of 2018, my colleagues and I played with LEGO® bricks in a corporate setting for a total of 16 hours. Many were open to the idea because they thought it would be fun and make for good team building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insta Strategy</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/instastrategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/instastrategy/</guid>
      <description>Six types of instagram posts for artists and creative professionals to promote their work
 Instagram a a social media platform has emerged a the most authentic way to represent yourself online. It&amp;rsquo;s simplicity and format provide a built-in bullshit filter. As a bonus, the interface makes the process of discovery, curation and promotion intuitive and user-friendly.  If we could only choose one social media platform it should be Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moments</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/moments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/moments/</guid>
      <description>Short text and images inspired by the now defunct hi.co. These quick sketches are quick meditations in the spirit of fugitive ground August 12, 2016 &amp;dash; Moment
 A man laboriously moves his piano down three levels onto the subway platform. Classic vocals and strided chords &amp;mdash; he played so well I swore he was blind. Oblivious to the heat on that August stage, he was most in touch with his audience &amp;mdash; whom he elevated with his music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data 2 Go</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/data2go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/data2go/</guid>
      <description>A summary of a Hyperact lunch talk about the creation of a web-based app called data2go.nyc   Data2go lunch talk notes and poster
  On Friday, 20 May 2016, Hyperact hyperakt.com/lunch-talks/ hosted a lunch talk with speaker Kristen Lewis. Kristen is the Co-director of Measure of America &amp;mdash; an organization that provides easy-to-use yet methodologically sound tools for understanding the distribution of well-being and opportunity in America and stimulating fact-based dialogue about issues we all care about: health, education, and living standards measureofamerica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory of the SSMAC of New York City</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/ssmac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/ssmac/</guid>
      <description>The club’s mission states: Serving the men and women of our Armed Forces since 1919 &amp;mdash; the club served me in my transition out of the military  Lounge at the SSMAC
   I have a strong connection between my transition out of the military and the The Soldiers&amp;rsquo;, Sailors&amp;rsquo;, Marines&amp;rsquo;, Coast Guard and Airmen&amp;rsquo;s Club (SSMAC) in New York City. Located on Lexington Avenue between 36th and 37th Streets, the SMAC wonderfully represents the strong connection NYC has to the uniformed services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Observing The Centennial</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/observing-the-cenntenial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/observing-the-cenntenial/</guid>
      <description>One hundred years later media, maps, websites and organizations to guide your commemoration of the war to end all wars WWI Soldiers in a dead Forest
From 2014 to 2018 we commemorate the centennial of &amp;#8220;The Great War,&amp;#8221; so-called because those who experienced it could imagine no conflict more terrible, and could not believe that the same disastrous mistakes could ever be repeated. Removed by as much as three generations from life today, the events of 1914&amp;#8211;18 hold lessons and truths about our humanity that could be lost&amp;#8202;&amp;#8212;&amp;#8202;or worse&amp;#8202;&amp;#8212;&amp;#8202;be rendered unbelievable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Day is not Memorial Day</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/veteransdayisnotmemorialday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/veteransdayisnotmemorialday/</guid>
      <description>Meaningful dialog on this often misunderstood holiday is needed &amp;mdash; we need to change the narrative and start to really understand what these holidays are about I was moved the other day by a radio story about a gold-star family (NPR) who lost their son, however, the story would have been more appropriate on Memorial Day. Overall, we need to change the narrative and start to really understand what these holidays (in this case Veterans Day) are about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surrealist Drawing Techniques</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/surrealistdrawingtechniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/surrealistdrawingtechniques/</guid>
      <description>A collection of drawing methods to exercise the mind and the role of the subconcious in art and design   Example frottage work from the Golden Gate Bridge
  Frottage Frottage from the French frotter, “to rub,” is a surrealist technique developed by Max Ernst. In Frottage the artist takes a pencil or other drawing tool and makes a rubbing over a textured surface. The resulting drawing can be used as-is, or used as a base for further refinement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Fontana, New Media Artist</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/fontana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/posts/fontana/</guid>
      <description>An artist&amp;rsquo;s installations making use of sound as a sculptural medium to transform the audience’s perceptions of visual and architectural settings Bill Fontana is a bit dry in interviews but he is big on sound. Bill attended the New School in New York City and studied music and philosophy. He is trained and practiced as a composer but he is known internationally for creating sound art. These installations use sound as a sculptural medium to transform the audience’s perceptions of visual and architectural settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/designclasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/designclasses/</guid>
      <description>Design Classes  var link = document.createElement( &#39;link&#39; ); link.rel = &#39;stylesheet&#39;; link.type = &#39;text/css&#39;; link.href = window.location.search.match( /print-pdf/gi ) ? &#39;css/print/pdf.css&#39; : &#39;css/print/paper.css&#39;; document.getElementsByTagName( &#39;head&#39; )[0].appendChild( link );          AGENDA 1. CLASSES:  Introduction to Interaction Design Visualizing Information  2. DISCUSSION: Professional Development    CLASSES   INTRODUCTION TO INTERACTION DESIGN   User Researcher Usability Analyst Information Architect    Interaction Designer Visual Designer UX Designer (all of the above)    Here is a link to Introductory Slides from Irene Pereyra   VISUALIZING INFORMATION    Documentary Exploratory Narrative Artistic    These types of visualizations are captured in many examples in Hilla Katki&#39;s Introductory Slides   For Your Reference Link to this presentation: andypbrowne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/howwespeak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/howwespeak/</guid>
      <description>How We Speak  var link = document.createElement( &#39;link&#39; ); link.rel = &#39;stylesheet&#39;; link.type = &#39;text/css&#39;; link.href = window.location.search.match( /print-pdf/gi ) ? &#39;css/print/pdf.css&#39; : &#39;css/print/paper.css&#39;; document.getElementsByTagName( &#39;head&#39; )[0].appendChild( link );       How We Speak Part 1: The Significance of Amplitude Typeface How We Speak, Speaker Notes. Prepared by Andrew Browne, May 2012.  Typography is the style and appearance of printed matter. A typeface is a family of fonts (like Helvetica or Futura), and a font is a particular weight of a typeface (like light, regular, medium, condensed or bold).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/mindthegap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/mindthegap/</guid>
      <description>Mind the Gap  var link = document.createElement( &#39;link&#39; ); link.rel = &#39;stylesheet&#39;; link.type = &#39;text/css&#39;; link.href = window.location.search.match( /print-pdf/gi ) ? &#39;css/print/pdf.css&#39; : &#39;css/print/paper.css&#39;; document.getElementsByTagName( &#39;head&#39; )[0].appendChild( link );        Mind the Gap Mind what gap?
The gap is the learning curve between graphic and web design. This lecture and workshop seeks to provide some tools, exercises, and approaches to mind the gap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/pres/services/</guid>
      <description>____ de$ign services  var link = document.createElement( &#39;link&#39; ); link.rel = &#39;stylesheet&#39;; link.type = &#39;text/css&#39;; link.href = window.location.search.match( /print-pdf/gi ) ? &#39;css/print/pdf.css&#39; : &#39;css/print/paper.css&#39;; document.getElementsByTagName( &#39;head&#39; )[0].appendChild( link );         
     HELLO DE$IGN SERVICES    __________ CORPORATE NON-PROFIT INDIVIDUAL AGENCY  DE$IGN1 SERVICES ①
Comprehensive
Branding  ②
Comprehensive
Website  ③
Logo design</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Andy is a Digital Designer in JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co.’s Chief Operating Office. He is a steward of the firm&amp;rsquo;s brand—he supports presentations and information design for digital and print products. Andy has worked for the firm’s Corporate and Investment Bank and Cybersecurity &amp;amp; Technology Controls for seven years in creative roles. He has a passion for visual design, user experience and web development.
A former US Army Captain—Andy served in the Infantry for seven years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Exhibitions 2014 | Fugitive Ground
The BogArt @ 56 Bogart Steet, Brooklyn, NY
2012 | Caught Mapping
Paul Seftel Project Space, Chelsea, NY
2011 | The Living Gallery
In Rivers, Artspace, Brooklyn, NY
2011 | Hope Act Love
Beach Street Gallery, NY, NY
2009 | Invisible Strings
Beach Street Gallery, NY, NY
Speaking Engagements 2018 | Creating a Big Bang Around Customer Experience with Atomic Design (panelist)
2016 | Creativity in Corporate De$ign</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caught Mapping</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/caughtmapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/caughtmapping/</guid>
      <description>A continuing collaboration between artists exploring cartography and invented landscapes   The CM newsprint reader sitting in a coffee shop
  A group of five long-time artist collaborators conceived of an exhibition called ++ Caught Mapping ++ at PS Project Space in the Chelsea Art District in New York City. The show took place over a period of 2 weeks in September 2012. The project continued a developing process called “The Living Gallery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cosmos</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/cosmos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/cosmos/</guid>
      <description>Editorial and graphic design by a favorite television show  A closeup of source material found in the image library at the New York Public Library  Cosmos is a student project from 2011. It is a 4-page editorial spread that appropriated the transcription of my favorite episode of Cosmos. The “Backbone of Night” is about the mystery and the compelling nature of the universe.
The theme of space was first created by a typography exercise called illustrated word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fan Art</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fan-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fan-art/</guid>
      <description> Fan Art and miscelaneous illustration  First ever known fan art for the instagram celebrity @bleuintheburg  Generally I do a lot of hand work that sits beside digital and web design work in the gallery. Often the two ways of working inform each other&amp;ndash; even flip back and forth between physical and digital.
 Illustration for a non-profit called Acts of Love - Ollie&#39;s Place Animal Rescue    Vine carcoal illustration for the Vital Key component of an exhibit called Hope Act Love   Call for entries, car-to-go   Collaborative exquisite corpse drawing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Ground</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fugitiveground/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fugitiveground/</guid>
      <description>Fugitive Ground is an ongoing collaboration with friends and fellow artists. The themes are centered around mindfulness, meditation, perception and art. The process of constructing print pieces, hosting workshops and developing web components provided the same kind of meditation prescribed by the project itself.  As development continues we can expect more print pieces and an evolving website. For now the website provides functionality for its contributors including general information, a mailing list, event information, and sun and moon data based on location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagramallation</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/instagramallation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/instagramallation/</guid>
      <description>A web experiment used for environmental design  Scene from an event called 2nd Life Remix   A collaborative project with Charles Wray originally designed as a fun experiment for a birthday parity in December 2012. It is important to note that this project is not a website &amp;mdash; the web is used in this case as environmental design.
 The project leverages unique instagram hashtags, IFTTT, google documents and a custom website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LP Backpack</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/lp-backpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/lp-backpack/</guid>
      <description>Organization/Client: Student project at the SVA MFA Interaction Design Continuing Education Interaction Design Course. Summer 2015.
My Role: User Research, Interaction Design
The Problem A fictional client needed to explore digital experiences to engage target audiences. We needed to find out who that audience was, thier needs, and prototype a new digital product.
Methods/Solutions: I conducted a traditional UX Research process (detailed below) and modeled experiences using flows and wireframes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Branding</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/personal-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/personal-branding/</guid>
      <description>A brand is not necessarily visual. It’s a promise of an experience  Sean Adams, as referenced in brand thinking and the definition of brand
  The goal of this project was to create a versatile and novel identity for use as a personal brand. This kind of project is supposed to represent all of our talent, wit and narcissism. Realistically though I knew this identity had to be more about process, experimentation and play&amp;mdash;because thats who I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romina Garber, Author Website</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/rominagarber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/rominagarber/</guid>
      <description>Beware the 13th Sign  Romina Garber, YA author, required a versatile blog. The purpose was mainly to support the launch of here first novel, ZODIAC. The site also features social media integration for essential components like twitter, tumblr, facebook and instagram.  Ideally this website&#39;s platform (WordPress) and framework (Zurb Foundation) are not apparent to the user. The visitor experiences a clean and content-first layout that is responsive and integrated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>