<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on andypbrowne</title>
    <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on andypbrowne</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://andypbrowne.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Caught Mapping</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/caughtmapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/caughtmapping/</guid>
      <description>The CM newsprint reader sitting in a coffee shop
  Agroup of five long-time artist collaborators conceived of an exhibition called ++ Caught Mapping ++ at PS Project Space in the Chelsea Art District in New York City. The show took place over a period of 2 weeks in September 2012. The project continued a developing process called “The Living Gallery.” Much of the work, presented ++ Caught Mapping ++ was created in the gallery itself and crafted in full view of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cosmos</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/cosmos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/cosmos/</guid>
      <description>Editorial and graphic design by a favorite television show Cosmos is a student project from 2011. It is a 4-page editorial spread that appropriated the transcription of my favorite episode of Cosmos. The “Backbone of Night” is about the mystery and the compelling nature of the universe.
The theme of space was first created by a typography exercise called illustrated word. I also like to think of it as words at play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fan Art</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fan-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fan-art/</guid>
      <description>Fan Art and miscelaneous illustration Generally I do a lot of hand work that sits beside digital and web design work in the gallery. Often the two ways of working inform each other&amp;ndash; even flip back and forth between physical and digital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Ground</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fugitiveground/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/fugitiveground/</guid>
      <description>Phont layoutTablet layoutDesktop layoutBushwick Open Studios, day of installationBushwick Open Studios, rehursal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagramallation</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/instagramallation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/instagramallation/</guid>
      <description>A web experiment used for environmental design </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LP Backpack</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/lp-backpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/lp-backpack/</guid>
      <description>Arobust student project, LP Backpack was created for a continuing education course at the School of the Visual Arts Interaction design program.
A series of design artifacts proposes a digital product for the fictional client Lonely Planet. Specifically this project included: 15+ user interviews, 3 generated personas, ecosystem and competitive analysis, card sorting exercises, MVP analysis, site map, features &amp;amp; functionality matrix, user flows and detailed annotated wireframes. The five week process concluded with a client presentation where this proposal was chosen as one of the top three out of twelve presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Branding</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/personal-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/personal-branding/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this project was to create a versatile and novel identity for use as a personal brand. This kind of project is supposed to represent all of our talent, wit and narcissism. Realistically though I knew this identity had to be more about process, experimentation and play—because thats who I am.
With this type of experimental approach we are free to really explore. In my exploration I sketched endlessly, re-learned Adobe Illustrator, carved a stamp, visited a laser cutting machine at Parsons and learned everything about SVG for the web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romina Garber, Author Website</title>
      <link>https://andypbrowne.com/work/rominagarber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andypbrowne.com/work/rominagarber/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>